A Guide to the Population Council records, Central Files, Accession 2, RG 2, Series 1 to Series 4 FA432
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2, Central Files, 1957-1983; bulk; 2; 286 Cubic Feet
  - Foreign Correspondence File, 2; 72.72 Cubic Feet 164 document boxes.
    - Thailand
      - United States Operations Mission to Thailand, 1960-1966 (Box 174, Folder 1673)
      - University of Medical Sciences, 1965-1968 (Box 174, Folder 1674)
      - U. S. Agency for International Development, 1968-1969 (Box 174, Folder 1675)
      - Dr. Nicholas H. Wright, 1973 (Box 174, Folder 1676)
    - Togo
      Togo
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1967, 1969-1974 (Box 174, Folder 1677)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Dr. S. I. Looky, 1971 (Box 174, Folder 1678)
    - Tonga
      Tonga
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1968, 1972-1973 (Box 174, Folder 1679)
    - Trinidad and Tobago
      Trinidad and Tobago
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1960, 1963-1964, 1967-1973 (Box 174, Folder 1680)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1971-1972 (Box 174, Folder 1681)
    - Trust Territory of the Pacific Islands
      Pacific Islands
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 174, Folder 1682)
    - Tunisia
      Tunisia
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1962-1967 (Box 175, Folder 1683)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1968 (Box 175, Folder 1684)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1969 (Box 175, Folder 1685)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1970 (Box 175, Folder 1686)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1971 (Box 175, Folder 1687)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1972 (Box 176, Folder 1688)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1973 January-June (Box 176, Folder 1689)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1973 July-December (Box 176, Folder 1690)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Cytology Program, 1971 (Box 176, Folder 1691)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Population Education Program Materials, 1969-1970 (Box 176, Folder 1692)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Population Education Program Materials, 1971 (Box 176, Folder 1693)
      - Family Planning Seminar, Tunis, January 22-February 6, 1964, 1963-1964 (Box 176, Folder 1694)
      - Ford Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 177, Folder 1695)
      - Ford Foundation, 1964-1968 (Box 177, Folder 1696)
      - Ford Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 177, Folder 1697)
      - Ford Foundation, 1971-1973 (Box 177, Folder 1698)
      - Dr. Jean-Claude Garnier, 1966, 1969 (Box 177, Folder 1699)
      - Joseph A. Grinblat, 1969-1971 (Box 177, Folder 1700)
      - Joseph A. Grinblat, 1972 (Box 177, Folder 1701)
      - Joseph A. Grinblat, 1973 (Box 177, Folder 1702)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1967-1971, 1973 (Box 178, Folder 1703)
      - Dr. Robert J. Lapham, 1968 (Box 178, Folder 1704)
      - Dr. Robert J. Lapham, 1969 (Box 178, Folder 1705)
      - Alain J. Marcoux, 1973 (Box 178, Folder 1706)
      - Ministry of Health, 1963-1968 (Box 178, Folder 1707)
      - Ministry of Health, 1969-1973 (Box 178, Folder 1708)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. George F. Brown, 1964-1965 (Box 178, Folder 1709)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. George F. Brown, 1966 (Box 178, Folder 1710)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. George F. Brown: Reports, 1964-1968 (Box 179, Folder 1711)
      - Ministry of Health: Equipment - Contraceptive Supplies, 1963-1964 (Box 179, Folder 1712)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Jacques Meylan, 1965 (Box 179, Folder 1713)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Jean Morsa, 1962-1967 (Box 179, Folder 1714)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. W. George Povey, 1966 (Box 179, Folder 1715)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. W. George Povey, 1967 January-July (Box 179, Folder 1716)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. W. George Povey, 1967 August-December (Box 179, Folder 1717)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. W. George Povey, 1968 (Box 179, Folder 1718)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Christopher Tietze, 1965-1966 (Box 180, Folder 1719)
      - Elisabeth E. Mueller, 1967-1968 (Box 180, Folder 1720)
      - Elisabeth E. Mueller, 1969 (Box 180, Folder 1721)
      - Elisabeth E. Mueller, 1970 (Box 180, Folder 1722)
      - Elisabeth E. Mueller, 1971-1972 (Box 180, Folder 1723)
      - Service Statistics Evaluation, 1972-1974 (Box 180, Folder 1724)
      - Dr. Melvyn C. Thorne, 1968 (Box 180, Folder 1725)
      - Dr. Melvyn C. Thorne, 1969 January-April (Box 181, Folder 1726)
      - Dr. Melvyn C. Thorne, 1969 May-July (Box 181, Folder 1727)
      - Dr. Melvyn C. Thorne, 1969 August-September (Box 181, Folder 1728)
      - Dr. Melvyn C. Thorne, 1969 October-December (Box 181, Folder 1729)
      - Dr. Melvyn C. Thorne, 1970 January-March (Box 181, Folder 1730)
      - Dr. Melvyn C. Thorne, 1970 April-June (Box 181, Folder 1731)
      - Dr. Melvyn C. Thorne, 1970 July-December (Box 182, Folder 1732)
      - Dr. Melvyn C. Thorne, 1971 (Box 182, Folder 1733)
      - Dr. Melvyn C. Thorne, 1972-1973 (Box 182, Folder 1734)
      - Tunis Study Work by Morsa (Folder 1 of 2), 1963 (Box 182, Folder 1735)
      - Tunis Study Work by Morsa (Folder 2 of 2), 1963 (Box 182, Folder 1736)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey, 1967-1969 (Box 182, Folder 1737)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey, 1970-1971 (Box 183, Folder 1738)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey, 1972 January-June (Box 183, Folder 1739)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey, 1972 July-1974 (Box 183, Folder 1740)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Analysis, Documents, Forms, Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 183, Folder 1741)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Bibliography of Articles, undated (Box 183, Folder 1742)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Birth and Death Summary Tables, 1968-1969, 1972 (Box 183, Folder 1743)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Calculations of Denominator Populations, 1969 (Box 183, Folder 1744)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Codes - Decks 1, 2 and 3 - Masters and Copies, 1968-1969 (Box 183, Folder 1745)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Codes - French - Deck 3, 1969 (Box 183, Folder 1746)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Coding Documents, undated (Box 183, Folder 1747)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Data Desired from Tunisian Census or Tunisian Demographic Survey, undated (Box 183, Folder 1748)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Detailed Analysis, 1969 (Box 183, Folder 1749)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Documents for Computer Analysis, 1969 (Box 183, Folder 1750)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Forms for Correcting Sample - 1969-1970, undated (Box 183, Folder 1751)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Karol J. Krotki, Tunisian Report, 1969 (Box 183, Folder 1752)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Motivation Survey, 1969 (Box 183, Folder 1753)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Reports, 1969 (Box 183, Folder 1754)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Sample Lists (Folder 1 of 3), 1968-1971 (Box 184, Folder 1755)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Sample Lists (Folder 2 of 3), 1968-1971 (Box 184, Folder 1756)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Sample Lists (Folder 3 of 3), 1968-1971 (Box 184, Folder 1757)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: William Seltzer, Notes on the Tunisian National Demographic Survey, 1968 (Box 184, Folder 1758)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Irving Sivin, Draft Report, 1969 (Box 184, Folder 1759)
      - Tunisian Demographic Survey: Jacques Vallin, Early Report on Proposed Tunisian Demographic Survey, 1967 (Box 184, Folder 1760)
      - Tunisian Mission on Family Planning, 1963-1964 (Box 184, Folder 1761)
      - Jacques Vallin, 1967-1968 (Box 184, Folder 1762)
      - Jacques Vallin, 1969 (Box 184, Folder 1763)
    - Turkey
      Turkey
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1959-1964 (Box 185, Folder 1764)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1965-1966 (Box 185, Folder 1765)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1967-1968 (Box 185, Folder 1766)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1969-1973 (Box 185, Folder 1767)
      - Correspondence, Report, Studies: Talas Grant Request, Kayseri Province, 1967 (Box 185, Folder 1768)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Visit to U. S. A. by Dr. Ahmet Ihsan Kirimli and Party, 1967 (Box 185, Folder 1769)
      - Advanced Seminar in the Social Sciences, Lake Abant, Bolu, Turkey, August 25-September 1, 1966 (Box 185, Folder 1770)
      - Ankara Gynecological Society, Dr. Necdet Erenus, 1963-1966 (Box 185, Folder 1771)
      - Development Foundation of Turkey, 1971-1972 (Box 185, Folder 1772)
      - Development Foundation of Turkey: Demographic Goals and Family Planning Project, 1972-1974 (Box 186, Folder 1773)
      - Economic and Social Studies Conference Board: Seminar, 1963-1965 (Box 186, Folder 1774)
      - Ford Foundation, 1961, 1963-1969, 1972-1973 (Box 186, Folder 1775)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen, 1966-1967 September (Box 186, Folder 1776)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen, 1967 October-December (Box 186, Folder 1777)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen, 1968 January-June (Box 186, Folder 1778)
      - Dr. John K. Friesen, 1968 July-December (Box 187, Folder 1779)
      - Hacettepe University, Institute of Population Studies, 1966-1968 (Box 187, Folder 1780)
      - Hacettepe University, Institute of Population Studies, 1969-1974 (Box 187, Folder 1781)
      - Hacettepe University, Institute of Population Studies: 1973 Survey of Population Problems in Turkey, Dr. Hsn A. Kinici, 1972-1973 (Box 187, Folder 1782)
      - International Cooperation Administration, 1962-1965 (Box 187, Folder 1783)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1967-1970, 1972-1973 (Box 187, Folder 1784)
      - S. M. (Sam) Keeny, Population Council Representative, 1965-1966 (Box 187, Folder 1785)
      - Ministry of Health, 1963-1964 (Box 188, Folder 1786)
      - Ministry of Health, 1965-1967 (Box 188, Folder 1787)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Lewis S. Anderson, 1965-1966 July (Box 188, Folder 1788)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Lewis S. Anderson, 1966 August-December (Box 188, Folder 1789)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Lewis S. Anderson, 1967 January-April (Box 188, Folder 1790)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Lewis S. Anderson, 1967 May-September (Box 189, Folder 1791)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Lewis S. Anderson, 1967 October-December (Box 189, Folder 1792)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Lewis S. Anderson, 1968 January-February (Box 189, Folder 1793)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Lewis S. Anderson, 1968 March-October (Box 189, Folder 1794)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Lewis S. Anderson, 1968 November-December (Box 189, Folder 1795)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Lewis S. Anderson, 1969 January-July (Box 190, Folder 1796)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Lewis S. Anderson, 1969 August-December (Box 190, Folder 1797)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Lewis S. Anderson, 1970 (Box 190, Folder 1798)
      - Ministry of Health: George W. Angell, Jr., 1963-1966 (Box 190, Folder 1799)
      - Ministry of Health: Russell H. Davis, Jr., 1964 (Box 190, Folder 1800)
      - Ministry of Health: Russell H. Davis, Jr., 1965 January-June (Box 190, Folder 1801)
      - Ministry of Health: Russell H. Davis, Jr., 1965 July-August (Box 190, Folder 1802)
      - Ministry of Health: Russell H. Davis, Jr., 1965 September-December (Box 191, Folder 1803)
      - Ministry of Health: Russell H. Davis, Jr., 1966 (Box 191, Folder 1804)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. Morey R. Fields, 1963 (Box 191, Folder 1805)
      - Ministry of Health: (Mrs.) Nuray Fincanciolu: IUD Follow-up Questionnaire, 1968-1969 (Box 191, Folder 1806)
      - Ministry of Health: Robert W. Gillespie, 1966 (Box 191, Folder 1807)
      - Ministry of Health: Law Concerning Population Planning, 1954, 1965 (Box 191, Folder 1808)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. John A. Ross, 1966 (Box 191, Folder 1809)
      - Ministry of Health: Dr. John A. Ross, 1967 (Box 191, Folder 1810)
      - Population Council Mission to Turkey, 1962-1963 (Box 191, Folder 1811)
      - Population Council Mission to Turkey: "Recommendations for a Population Planning Program for the Republic of Turkey", 1963 (Box 192, Folder 1812)
      - State Planning Organization, 1960-1964 (Box 192, Folder 1813)
      - Turkish Family Planning Association, 1966-1967, 1969-1970 (Box 192, Folder 1814)
      - University of Istanbul, 1961-1967, 1970, 1973 (Box 192, Folder 1815)
      - University of Istanbul: IBM Equipment, 1965-1970 (Box 192, Folder 1816)
      - U. S. Agency for International Development, 1965-1972 (Box 192, Folder 1817)
    - Uganda
      Uganda
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1963-1964, 1966-1972 (Box 192, Folder 1818)
      - American Friends Service Committee: Dr. George Saxton: Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 192, Folder 1819)
      - Family Planning Association of Uganda, 1965-1967, 1969 (Box 192, Folder 1820)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1969 (Box 192, Folder 1821)
      - Makerere University, 1966-1971 (Box 192, Folder 1822)
      - Makerere University: Dr. George Saxton, 1964-1969 (Box 192, Folder 1823)
      - Melvin L. Perlman, 1960-1961 (Box 192, Folder 1824)
      - Stephen R. Taber, 1968-1972 (Box 192, Folder 1825)
      - Stephen R. Taber: Country Agreement, 1969 (Box 192, Folder 1826)
    - Uruguay
      Uruguay
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1965-1968, 1970 (Box 192, Folder 1827)
    - Venezuela
      Venezuela
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1958-1960, 1963-1966 (Box 193, Folder 1828)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1967-1969 (Box 193, Folder 1829)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1970-1973 (Box 193, Folder 1830)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Pan American Congress of Pharmacy and Biochemistry, 1972 (Box 193, Folder 1831)
      - Fertility in the Venezuelan Guayana: (Mrs.) Leatrice D. MacDonald: Two Grant Proposals, 1964 (Box 193, Folder 1832)
      - Ministry of Health, 1966-1968 (Box 193, Folder 1833)
      - Dr. Adaline P. (Penny) Satterthwaite, 1971 (Box 193, Folder 1834)
      - Dr. Adaline P. (Penny) Satterthwaite, 1972 January-March (Box 193, Folder 1835)
      - Dr. Adaline P. (Penny) Satterthwaite, 1972 April-December (Box 193, Folder 1836)
      - Dr. Adaline P. (Penny) Satterthwaite, 1973 (Box 194, Folder 1837)
      - Dr. Adaline P. (Penny) Satterthwaite: Diary Notes, 1971 (Box 194, Folder 1838)
      - Dr. Adaline P. (Penny) Satterthwaite: Diary Notes, 1972 (Box 194, Folder 1839)
      - Dr. Adaline P. (Penny) Satterthwaite: Diary Notes, 1973 (Box 194, Folder 1840)
      - Universidad Catolica Andres Bello, 1966, 1968 (Box 194, Folder 1841)
    - Vietnam
      Vietnam
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1960, 1963, 1966-1968 (Box 194, Folder 1842)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1969-1971 (Box 194, Folder 1843)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 195, Folder 1844)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Cytology Training, 1969 (Box 195, Folder 1845)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: IUD's to North Vietnam, 1973 (Box 195, Folder 1846)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1967 (Box 195, Folder 1847)
      - U. S. Agency for International Development, 1966-1970, 1972 (Box 195, Folder 1848)
    - West Indies
      West Indies
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1967, 1969-1970, 1972-1973 (Box 195, Folder 1849)
      - The Beth Jacobs Clinic, Ltd., 1961-1963 (Box 195, Folder 1850)
      - Dr. Dudley Kirk: Travel, 1960 (Box 195, Folder 1851)
      - University College of the West Indies: Census Research Programme, 1958-1960 (Box 195, Folder 1852)
      - University College of the West Indies: Census Research Programme, 1961 (Box 195, Folder 1853)
      - University College of the West Indies: Census Research Programme, 1962-1966 (Box 195, Folder 1854)
    - Yugoslavia
      Yugoslavia
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1961-1967, 1970-1973 (Box 195, Folder 1855)
      - KAP (Knowledge, Attitude, Practice) Survey, 1972-1973 (Box 195, Folder 1856)
    - Zaire
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1971-1974 (Box 195, Folder 1857)
    - Zambia
      Zambia
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1965, 1967-1969, 1973-1974 (Box 195, Folder 1858)
      - Correspondence, Reports, Studies: Dr. Patrick O. Ohadike: Thesis Publication, 1968-1969 (Box 195, Folder 1859)
    - Monthly Reports
      - Ceylon
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 (Box 196, Folder 1860)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 (Box 196, Folder 1861)
        - Monthly Reports, 1969 (Box 196, Folder 1862)
      - Ghana: Africa Regional Office
        - Monthly Reports, 1971 (Box 196, Folder 1863)
        - Monthly Reports, 1972 (Box 196, Folder 1864)
      - Iran
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 (Box 196, Folder 1865)
        - Monthly Reports, 1969 (Box 196, Folder 1866)
        - Monthly Reports, 1970 (Box 196, Folder 1867)
        - Monthly Reports, 1971 (Box 196, Folder 1868)
        - Monthly Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 196, Folder 1869)
      - Kenya
        - Monthly Reports, 1966 (Box 196, Folder 1870)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 (Box 196, Folder 1871)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 (Box 196, Folder 1872)
        - Monthly Reports, 1969 (Box 196, Folder 1873)
        - Monthly Reports, 1970 (Box 196, Folder 1874)
        - Monthly Reports, 1971 (Box 196, Folder 1875)
        - Monthly Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 196, Folder 1876)
      - Korea
        - Monthly Reports, 1966 October (Box 197, Folder 1877)
        - Monthly Reports, 1966 November (Box 197, Folder 1878)
        - Monthly Reports, 1966 December (Box 197, Folder 1879)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 January (Box 197, Folder 1880)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 February (Box 197, Folder 1881)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 March (Box 197, Folder 1882)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 April (Box 197, Folder 1883)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 May (Box 197, Folder 1884)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 June (Box 197, Folder 1885)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 July (Box 197, Folder 1886)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 August (Box 197, Folder 1887)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 September (Box 197, Folder 1888)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 October (Box 197, Folder 1889)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 November (Box 197, Folder 1890)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 December (Box 197, Folder 1891)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 January (Box 198, Folder 1892)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 February (Box 198, Folder 1893)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 March (Box 198, Folder 1894)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 April (Box 198, Folder 1895)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 May (Box 198, Folder 1896)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 June (Box 198, Folder 1897)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 July (Box 198, Folder 1898)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 August (Box 198, Folder 1899)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 September (Box 198, Folder 1900)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 October (Box 198, Folder 1901)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 November (Box 198, Folder 1902)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 December (Box 198, Folder 1903)
        - Monthly Reports, 1969 January-June (Box 198, Folder 1904)
        - Monthly Reports, 1969 July-December (Box 198, Folder 1905)
        - Monthly Reports, 1970 (Box 198, Folder 1906)
        - Monthly Reports, 1971 (Box 199, Folder 1907)
        - Monthly Reports, 1972 (Box 199, Folder 1908)
      - Morocco
        - Monthly Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 199, Folder 1909)
        - Monthly Reports, 1969 (Box 199, Folder 1910)
        - Monthly Reports, 1970 (Box 199, Folder 1911)
        - Monthly Reports, 1971 (Box 199, Folder 1912)
      - Nigeria
        - Monthly Reports, 1969, 1971-1973 (Box 199, Folder 1913)
      - Pakistan
        - Monthly Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 199, Folder 1914)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 (Box 199, Folder 1915)
        - East Pakistan: Monthly Reports, 1967 (Box 200, Folder 1916)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 (Box 200, Folder 1917)
        - Monthly Reports, 1969-1973 (Box 200, Folder 1918)
      - Peru
        - Monthly Reports, 1972 (Box 200, Folder 1919)
      - Philippines
        - Monthly Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 200, Folder 1920)
      - Singapore
        - Monthly Reports, 1975 (Box 200, Folder 1921)
      - Taiwan: East Asia
        - Monthly Reports, 1964, 1966 (Box 200, Folder 1922)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 January-July (Box 200, Folder 1923)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 August-December (Box 200, Folder 1924)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 (Box 200, Folder 1925)
        - Monthly Reports, 1969 (Box 200, Folder 1926)
        - Monthly Reports, 1970 January-May (Box 201, Folder 1927)
        - Monthly Reports, 1970 June-December (Box 201, Folder 1928)
        - Monthly Reports, 1971 (Box 201, Folder 1929)
        - Monthly Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 201, Folder 1930)
      - Thailand
        - Monthly Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 201, Folder 1931)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 January-June (Box 201, Folder 1932)
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 July-December (Box 201, Folder 1933)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 (Box 201, Folder 1934)
        - Monthly Reports, 1969 January-April (Box 202, Folder 1935)
        - Monthly Reports, 1969 May-July (Box 202, Folder 1936)
        - Monthly Reports, 1969 August-December (Box 202, Folder 1937)
        - Monthly Reports, 1970 January-June (Box 202, Folder 1938)
        - Monthly Reports, 1970 July-August (Box 202, Folder 1939)
        - Monthly Reports, 1970 September-December (Box 202, Folder 1940)
        - Monthly Reports, 1971 January-April (Box 203, Folder 1941)
        - Monthly Reports, 1971 May-September (Box 203, Folder 1942)
        - Monthly Reports, 1971 October-December (Box 203, Folder 1943)
      - Tunisia
        - Monthly Reports, 1965-1967 (Box 203, Folder 1944)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 (Box 203, Folder 1945)
        - Monthly Reports, 1969 (Box 203, Folder 1946)
        - Monthly Reports, 1970 (Box 203, Folder 1947)
      - Turkey
        - Monthly Reports, 1967 (Box 203, Folder 1948)
        - Monthly Reports, 1968 (Box 203, Folder 1949)
        - Monthly Reports, 1969 (Box 203, Folder 1950)
        - Monthly Reports, 1970 (Box 203, Folder 1951)
  - Administration File, 3; 110.4 Cubic Feet Boxes 204-479.
    Primarily arranged by last name of Council staff.
    Indexing to the Administration File is provided by FA775 Population Council records, Index, Series 2: Central File Index, 1961-1976.
    Separated Materials
    Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the body of the Administration File and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
    - Biomedical Division - Correspondence, Reports, Studies, 1967; 1969; 1979 (Box 204, Folder 1952)
    - Biomedical Division - Formation of Committee on Physiology of Reproduction, 1953-1955 (Box 204, Folder 1953)
    - Biomedical Division - Biomedical Fellowship Awards, 1968-1970 (Box 204, Folder 1954)
    - Biomedical Division - Biomedical Fellowship Awards, 1966-1967 (Box 204, Folder 1955)
    - Biomedical Division - Scheaver, S. Bruce, Accounting, 1973 (Box 204, Folder 1956)
    - Biomedical Division - Segal, Sheldon J. - Memos, Correspondence, Segal's memo on conditions in India, (1970 March 2) 1967-1972 (Box 204, Folder 1957)
    - Biomedical Division - Consultants - Tatum, Howard - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 204, Folder 1958)
    - Biomedical Division - Tietze, Christopher - Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 204, Folder 1959)
    - Anderson, Richmond K. - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 205, Folder 1960)
    - Anderson, Richmond K. - Correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 205, Folder 1961)
    - Anderson, Richmond K. - Diary Notes, 1969 (Box 205, Folder 1962)